{
    "subject": "resource/GG_Allin",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedBand",
    "object": "resource/The_Jabbers",
    "human_readable": "GG Allin was associated with The Jabbers.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8394779562950134,
            "question": "What was GG Allin associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6895106434822083,
            "question": "What was the name of the group associated with GG Allin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5709494948387146,
            "question": "Who was part of The Jabbers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5281913876533508,
            "question": "Who were some notable members of The Jabbers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.505496084690094,
            "question": "Was GG Allin involved in any musical groups?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4469800591468811,
            "question": "What was The Jabbers known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42495352029800415,
            "question": "Name a group that GG Allin was connected to."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34627097845077515,
            "question": "What musical collective did GG Allin belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.332454115152359,
            "question": "Was GG Allin a part of any musical collaborations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24850675463676453,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a band or group that GG Allin worked with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=GG Allin was associated with The Jabbers.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8512_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was GG Allin a part of any musical collaborations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8512_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical collective did GG Allin belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8512_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a group that GG Allin was connected to.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8512_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8512_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8512_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8512_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8512_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8512_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8512_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8512_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8512_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8512_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8512_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that GG Allin played with the band The Jabbers, which supports the statement that GG Allin was associated with The Jabbers."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}